Guide to the A. Sidney Lovett Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- WRITINGS AND MISCELLANEA, 1900-1979; Series V; 4 linear feet (11 boxes)
  - Writings
    - Manuscripts, 1900-1917, undated (Box 70, Folder 669-677)
    - Matriculation services, 1932-1958 (Box 71, Folder 678)
    - Memorial services, 1933-1975, undated (Box 71, Folder 679-684)
    - Notebooks, 1904-1905; 1920; undated (Box 71, Folder 685-689)
    - Notebooks, undated (Box 72, Folder 690-693)
    - Notes, undated (Box 72, Folder 694-695)
    - Ordination prayers, undated (Box 72, Folder 696-697)
    - Plays, undated (Box 72, Folder 698)
    - Prayers, undated (Box 72, Folder 699)
    - Prayers and memorials, 1934-1958 (Box 72, Folder 700-702)
    - Prayers and memorials, 1964-1969, undated (Box 73, Folder 703-708)
    - Speeches, 1949-1957, undated (Box 73, Folder 709-710)
    - Speeches and sermons, 1912-1917, undated (Box 73, Folder 711-713)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 73, Folder 714-717)
  - Photographs: Class of 1913 and miscellanea, 1952-1953, undated (Box 74, Folder 718-723)
  - Printed material
    - Announcements--Yale Alumni Magazine, 1906-1979 (Box 75, Folder 724-740)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine--Yale University, general, 1908-1978 (Box 76, Folder 741-749)
  - Memorabilia, undated (Box 76, Folder 750)
  - Audio tapes and films
    - "Computers for the Humanities", 1965 (Box 77)
    - Films, undated (Box 77)
    - Films, undated (Box 78)
    - Films, undated (Box 79)